Guide to the Richard Bonelli Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Sound recordings
  - Richard Bonelli air checks IV (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Side A: Sailor's Life -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera -- Friml, Rudolf, 1879-1972. Three Musketeers -- Homer, Sidney, 1864-1953. Banjo song -- Buzzi-Peccia. Lolita -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Di Provenza il mar -- Along tobacco road -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. An Sylvia -- Golde, Walter, 1887-1963. Love was with me yesterday -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Stone. Brothers of Romany -- Yradier, Sebastián, 1809-1865. Paloma -- Burleigh, Henry Thacker, 1866-1949. Deep river (arr.) -- Trad. Run, Mary, run -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Serse. Ombra mai fù -- Martin, Easthope, 1875?-1925. More songs of the fair. Come to the fair -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Danse macabre (Song) -- Tally Ho! -- Youmans, Vincent, 1898-1946. Through the years -- Korngold, Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Danse macabre (Song) -- Taylor. Captain Stratton's fancy -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Balen del suo sorriso; Per me ora fatale.Side B: Damrosch, Walter, 1862-1950. Danny Deever -- Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Chanson du toréador -- Youmans, Vincent, 1898-1946. Through the years -- Friml, Rudolf, 1879-1972. Vagabond king. Love me tonight -- Damrosch, Walter, 1862-1950. Captain, O my captain -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Balen del suo sorriso -- Tennyson; Golde. Beauty, passing beauty -- Margetson, Edward, 1891-1962. Tommy, lad -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Israel in Egyp; Dank sei dir Herr (also attributed to Ochs, Siegfried) -- Trad. Swing low, sweet chariot -- Hardy, Edith. Colette -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Kuntz. Sleigh -- Tennyson; Golde. Beauty, passing beauty -- Horsman, E. A. (Ernest Alan), 1918-, Bird of wilderness -- Margetson, Edward, 1891-1962. Tommy, lad -- Speaks, Oley, 1876-1948. When the boys come home.
  - Air checks (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Leoncavallo, Ruggero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Prologue -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Korngold, Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Balen del suo sorriso -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. O du mein holder Abendstern -- Trad. Swing low, sweet chariot -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Andrea Chénier -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Hérodiade. Vision fugitive -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Roi de Lahore. Promesse de mon avenir -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Largo.
  - Town Hall Recital I (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Town Hall Recital II (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Town Hall Recital III (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Original tape of arias1969 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Di Provenza il mar -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. O du mein holder Abendstern -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera. Eri tu -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Andrea Chénier. Nemico della patria; Fedora. Donna russa -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Zazà. Zazà, piccola zingara -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Otello. Credo in un Dio crudel.
  - Miscellaneous ariasFeb. 3, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen -- Leoncavallo, Ruggero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Prologue -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Di Provenza il mar -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. O du mein holder Abendstern -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera. Eri tu -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Andrea Chénier. Nemico della patria; Fedora. Donna russa -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Zazà. Zazà, piccola zingara -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Otello. Credo in un Dio crudel.
  - Miscellaneous arias (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen -- Leoncavallo, Ruggero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Prologue.
  - Miscellaneous arias (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Di Provenza il mar -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. O du mein holder Abendstern
  - Miscellaneous arias (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera. Eri tu -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Andrea Chénier. Nemico della patria.
  - Miscellaneous arias (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Fedora. Donna russa -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Zazà. Zazà, piccola zingara -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Otello. Credo in un Dio crudel.
  - Miscellaneous arias (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Winterstürme wichen dem Wonnemond -- Monna Vanna [sic] ? --Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Zazà. Zazà, piccola zingara -- Speech
  - Miscellaneous arias (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Copy of arias made by R. Jones. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Winterstürme wichen dem Wonnemond -- Monna Vanna [sic] ?--Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Zazà. Zazà, piccola zingara -- Leoncavallo, Ruggero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Prologue
  - Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Pelléas et Mélisande (Box 33, Folder 14)
    Acts III, IV and V
  - Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Pelléas et Mélisande (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Rosenkavalier (Opera) (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Vocal excerpts. Los Angeles Symphony. Basile, Arturo, conductor. Della Casa, Lisa as Marzelina; Warenskjold, Dorothy as Sophie; Miller, Mildred, 1924-, as Octavian.
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Don Giovanni (Box 34, Folder 17)
    Excerpts. Metropolitan Opera.
  - Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. ToscaJan. 28, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Complete. London orchestra. Molinari-Pradelli, Francesco, conductor. Tebaldi, Renata; Del Monaco, Mario, 1915-,
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde (Box 34, Folder 19)
    Act I and II. Flagstad, Kirsten, 1895-1962; Suthaus, Ludwig; Thebom, Blanche
  - Cortis, Antonio, 1891-1952 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    Side A: Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Africaine. O paradis sorti de l'onde -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Andrea Chénier. Credo a una possanza -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Bohème. Che gelida manina -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Salut, demeure chaste et pure -- Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Fleur que tu m'avais jetée -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. Ah! fuyez, douce image -- Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Iris. Apri la tua finestra -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Werther. Pourquoi me réveiller -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Turandot. Non piangere, Liù.Side B: Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Turandot. Nessun dorma -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Werther. J'aurais sur ma poitrine; Pourquoi me réveiller -- Demone. Deh non plorar [sic] ? -- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Evgenii Onegin. Stsena i ariia Onegina -- Hérold, Ferdinand, 1791-1833. Zampa. Pourquoi trembler -- Berlioz, Hector, 1803-1869. Damnation de Faust. Voici des roses -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera. Eri tu -- Cocchi. Per la patria: Bella Italia.
  - Björling, Jussi, 1911-1960. (Box 34, Folder 21)
    Side A: Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto. Donna è mobile -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. Recondita armonia; E lucevan le stelle -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Stride la vampa -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Salut, demeure chaste et pure -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Bohème. O soave fanciulla -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Fedora. Amor ti vieta; Andrea Chénier. Come un bel dì di maggio -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Roméo et Juliette. Ah! lève-toi, soleil -- Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Fleur que tu m'avais jetée -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Elisir d'amore. Furtiva lagrima -- Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Africaine. O paradis sorti de l'onde -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. En fermant les yeux je vois; Ah! fuyez, douce image -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Manon Lescaut. Donna non vidi mai -- Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Cavalleria rusticana. O Lola -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Bohème. Che gelida manina -- Cilèa, Francesco, 1866-1950. Arlesiana. Pastore -- Ponchielli, Amilcare, 1834-1886. Gioconda. Cielo e mar .Side B: Ponchielli, Amilcare, 1834-1886. Gioconda. Cielo e mar -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto. Questa o quella per me pari sono -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Vesti la giubba -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Turandot. Nessun dorma.
  - Arias and Lieder by various singers (Box 34, Folder 22)
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde. O sink' hernieder. Melchior, Lauritz -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Arabella. So wie sie sind. Fuchs, Marta and Schöffler, Paul, 1897-, -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Salome. Lawrence, Marjorie -- Humperdinck, Engelbert, 1854-1921. Hänsel und Gretel. Gluck, Alma, 1884-1938 -- Adeste Fidelis. McCormack, John, 1884-1945 -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Hirt auf dem Felsen. Maynor, Dorothy -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Rethberg, Elizabeth -- Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Africaine. O paradis sorti de l'onde.
  - Sopranos. Demonstration transcriptions. (Box 34, Folder 23)
    Robin, Mado -- Kurz, Selma, 1874-1933 -- Angeles, María de los -- Boninsegna, Celestina, 1877-1947 -- Turner, Eva, Dame, 1892-1990 -- Ponselle, Rosa, 1897-1981 -- Telva, Marion. Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Turandot. In questa reggia. Turner, Eva, Dame, 1892-1990 -- Bellini, Vincenzo, 1801-1835. Norma. Mira, o Norma. Ponselle, Rosa, 1897-1981 and Telva, Marion.
  - Basses and Baritones (Box 34, Folder 24)
    Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Caïd. Air du tambour-major -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Fille du régiment. Au bruit de la guerre. Plançon, Pol, 1854-1914, bass -- illegible entry -- Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Huguenots. Piff, paff. Mardones, José, 1868-1932, bass -- Bellini, Vincenzo, 1801-1835. Puritani. Ah per sempre io ti perdei. Battistini, Mattia, 1856-1928, baritone -- Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Pardon de Ploërmel -- Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Hamlet. Comme une pâle fleur. Ruffo, Titta, 1877-1953, baritone -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Turandot. Tanto amore segreto. Magini-Coletti, Antonio, 1855-1912, baritone -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Vêpres siciliennes. Au sein de la puissance. Stracciari, Riccardo, baritone -- Catalani, Alfredo, 1854-1893. Wally. Viglione-Borghese, Domenico, 1877-1957, baritone -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Fedora. Donna russa. Bonelli, Richard, baritone.
  - Brahms and Sibelius (Box 34, Folder 25)
    Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 2, op. 83, Bb major. Chicago Symphony Orchestra. Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-, conductor. Richter, Sviatoslav, 1915-, piano -- Sibelius, Jean, 1865-1957. Symphony, no. 5, op. 82, Eb major; Pohjolan tytär. Boston Symphony Orchestra. Koussevitzky, Serge, 1874-1951, conductor.
  - Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Deutsches Requiem Apr. 17, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Deutsches Requiem. Mormon Tabernacle Choir. Schreiner, Alexander, 1901-, organ. Sayre, Fern, soprano. Bonelli, Richard, baritone.
  - Chausson and BrahmsApr. 6, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    Chausson, Ernest, 1855-1899. Poème de l'amour et de la mer. London Philharmonic. Froment, Louis de, conductor. Kolassi, Irma, 1918-, mezzo-soprano -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 2, op. 83, Bb major. Chicago Symphony Orchestra. Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-, conductor
  - Chausson, Franck and Mussorgsky (Box 34, Folder 28)
    Chausson, Ernest, 1855-1899. Symphony, op. 20, Bb major. Pasdeloup Orchestra [sic] -- unclear entry -- Franck, César, 1822-1890. Symphony, D minor. NBC Orchestra. Cantelli, Guido, conductor -- Mussorgsky, Modest Petrovich, 1839-1881. Night on Bald Mountain. Paris Conservatory Orchestra. Ansermet, Ernest, 1883-1969
  - Debussy, Strauss and Griffes (Box 35, Folder 29)
    Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Jeux. French Radio Orchestra -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Rosenkavalier. Suite. London Symphony Orchestra. Steinberg, William, conductor -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Damoiselle élue. Boston Symphony Orchestra. Munch, Charles, 1891-1968, conductor. Angeles, Victoria de los, soprano -- Griffes, Charles Tomlinson, 1884-1920. Fantasy pieces. Scherzo; arr. Eastman Orchestra. Hanson, Howard, 1896-, conductor.
  - Debussy, Strauss and Stravinsky (Box 34, Folder 30)
    Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Martyre de saint Sébastien. Boston Ensemble. Munch, Charles, 1891-1968, conductor -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Till Eulenspiegels lustige Streiche. Cleveland Orchestra. Rodzinski, Artur, 1892-1958, conductor -- Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Zhar-ptitsa. Suite (1945). Philadelphia Orchestra. Stokowski, Leopold, 1882-1977, conductor.
  - Debussy (Box 34, Folder 31)
    Side 1: Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Petite suite. Orchestra ?. Slatkin, Felix, conductor -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung. Brünnhildes Schlussgesang; Side 2: Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde. Prelude; Liebestod. Boston Symphony. Munch, Charles, 1891-1968, conductor. Farrell, Eileen, 1920-2002, soprano.
  - Glazunov and Wagner (Box 34, Folder 32)
    Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich, 1865-1936. Raimonda. Paris Philharmonic Orchestra. Rosenthal, Manuel, 1904-, conductor -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde. Liebestod; Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung. Brünnhildes Schlussgesang. Flagstad, Kirsten, 1895-1962, soprano.
  - Glière, Reinhold Moritsevich, 1875-1956. Symphony, no. 3, op. 42, B minor. May 4, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    Glière, Reinhold Moritsevich, 1875-1956. Symphony, no. 3, op. 42, B minor. Philadelphia Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor.
  - Pizetti, Ravel and Respighi (Box 35, Folder 34)
    Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1880-1968. Assassinio nella cattedrale. Rossi-Lemeni, Nicola, 1920-, bass -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Valses nobles et sentimentales; Valse -- Respighi, Ottorino, 1879-1936. Fontane di Roma. NBC Orchestra. Toscanini, Arturo, 1867-1957, conductor -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Miroirs. Alborada del gracioso. Hollywood Bowl. Slatkin, Leonard, conductor.
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Concertos, piano, no. 1 and no.3 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Concerto, piano, no. 1, op. 1, F [sharp] minor. Philadelphia Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor. Rachmaninoff, Sergei, piano; Romansy, op. 34. Vocalise; arr.; Concerto, piano, no. 3, op. 30, D minor. Philadelphia Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor. Rachmaninoff, Sergei, piano.
  - Rachmaninoff, Strauss, Borodin and Gounod (Box 35, Folder 36)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Concerto, piano, no. 1, op. 1, F [sharp] minor -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Burlesque, piano, orchestra, TrV 145, D minor. Chicago Symphony Orchestra. Reiner, Fritz, 1888-1963, conductor. Janis, Byron, piano -- Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Arianna. Lasciatemi morire. Gatti, Gabriella, soprano -- Borodin, Aleksandr Porfir«evich, 1833-1887. Kniaz« Igor«. Ariia kniazia Igoria -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Prenez mon bras. Quartet. Crooks, Richard, 1900-1972, tenor; Jepson, Helen, 1904-, soprano; Browning, Lucielle, alto; Pinza, Ezio, bass.
  - Rachmaninoff and Auber (Box 35, Folder 37)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Concerto, piano, no. 3, op. 30, D minor. Boston Symphony Orchestra. Munch, Charles, 1891-1968, conductor. Janis, Byron, piano -- Auber, D. F. E. (Daniel François Esprit), 1782-1871. Habanera. Paris Opera Orchestra -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 2, op. 18, C minor. Philadelphia Orchestra. Stokowski, Leopold, 1882-1977, conductor.
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. (Box 35, Folder 38)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Concerto, piano, no. 4, op. 40, G minor; Symphony, no. 3, op. 44, A minor. Philadelphia Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Rapsodie sur un thème de PaganiniMar. 5, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Rapsodie sur un thème de Paganini. London Symphony Orchestra. Stokowski, Leopold, 1882-1977, conductor. Moiseiwitsch, Benno, 1890-1963, piano.
  - Rachmaninoff and Puccini (Box 35, Folder 40)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Symphony, no. 1, op. 13, D minor. Dresden Symphony Orchestra -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. Act I. Tebaldi, Renata, soprano, et al (sic).
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Symphony, no. 2, op. 27, E minor. (Box 35, Folder 41)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Symphony, no. 2, op. 27, E minor. Minneapolis Symphony Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor.
  - Rachmaninoff and Borodin (Box 35, Folder 42)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Symphonic dances. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor -- Borodin, Aleksandr Porfir«evich, 1833-1887. Kniaz« Igor«. Polovetskaia pliaska. French National Orchestra. Markevitch, Igor, 1912-1983, conductor -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Concerto, piano, no. 1, op. 1, F [sharp] minor.
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. (Box 36, Folder 43)
    Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Romansy, op. 34. Vocalise; arr. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor; Ostrov mertvykh. Suisse Romande Orchestra. Ansermet, Ernest, 1883-1969, conductor; Kolokola. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor.
  - Ravel, Debussy, and Ibert (Box 36, Folder 44)
    Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Shéhérazade (Song cycle). Paris Conservatory Orchestra. Danco, Suzanne, soprano; Daphnis et Chloé. Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Images, orchestra. Ibéria. Detroit Symphony Orchestra. Paray, Paul, 1886-, conductor -- Ibert, Jacques, 1890-1962. Escales. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor.
  - Ravel and Stravinsky (Box 36, Folder 45)
    Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Tzigane. Francescatti, Zino, 1902-, violin; Shéhérazade (Song cycle). Suisse Romande Orchestra. Ansermet, Ernest, 1883-1969, conductor .Danco, Suzanne, soprano -- Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Petrushka. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Stokowski, Leopold, 1882-1977, conductor.
  - Respighi and Dvorák (Box 36, Folder 46)
    Respighi, Ottorino, 1879-1936. Feste romane. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor -- Dvorák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Symphony, no. 4, D minor.
  - Schoenberg, Delius and Debussy (Box 36, Folder 47)
    Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Verklärte Nacht. Stokowski, Leopold, 1882-1977, conductor -- Delius, Frederick, 1862-1934. Brigg Fair. Royal Philharmonic. Beecham, Thomas, Sir, 1879-1961, conductor -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Mer. Concertgebouw Orchestra. Beinum, Eduard van, conductor.
  - Sibelius, Jean, 1865-1957. (Box 36, Folder 48)
    Sibelius, Jean, 1865-1957. Lemminkäinen Overture; Tapiola. Boult, Adrian, Sir, 1889-, conductor; Pelléas et Mélisande. London Symphony Orchestra. Collins, Anthony, 1893-1963, conductor; Karelia. Suite. Danish Radio Symohony. Jensen, Thomas, 1898-1963, conductor; Symphony no. 7, op. 105, C major. London Symphony Orchestra. Collins, Anthony, 1893-1963, conductor; At the drawbridge (?) Royal Philharmonic. Beecham, Thomas, Sir, 1879-1961, conductor
  - Sibelius and Wagner (Box 36, Folder 49)
    Sibelius, Jean, 1865-1957. Symphony, no. 6, op. 104, D minor. Karajan, Herbert von, conductor -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Parsifal. Vorspiel; Charfreitagszauber. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Stokowski, Leopold, 1882-1977, conductor. -- Sibelius, Jean, 1865-1957. Symphony, no. 1, op. 39, E minor. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor.
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. (Box 36, Folder 50)
    Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Don Juan; Also sprach Zarathustra
  - Tchaikovsky and Loeffler (Box 36, Folder 51)
    Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Concerto, piano, no. 1, op. 23, Bb minor -- Loeffler, Charles Martin, 1861-1935. Pagan poem.
  - Wagner, Ives, Mozart and StraussJuly 2, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Meistersinger. Overture -- Ives, Charles, 1874-1954. Contemplations. Unanswered question -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Symphony, K. 385, D major -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Heldenleben. Hollywood Bowl Opening. Karajan, Herbert von, conductor.
  - Atwater Kent Hour. WABCOct.15, 1934, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Through the years -- Play Gypsies
  - Atwater Kent Hour. W.A.B.COct.15, 1934, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    La barcheta -- L'amour, tojours l'amour
  - Ford Symphony HourDec.23, 1934, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- I'll take you home again -- Kathleen
  - Chase and Sanborn Hour. W.E.A.FJan.6, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880. Contes d'Hoffmann. Opening; Belle nuit
  - Chase and Sanborn Hour. W.E.A.FJan.6, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880. Contes d'Hoffmann. Selections.
  - Chase and Sanborn Hour. W.E.A.FJan.6, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Chase and Sanborn Hour. W.E.A.FJan.6, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. 2. Akt. Jan.12, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.CDec.23, 1934, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Hérodiade. Vision fugitive -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.CDec.23, 1934, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Hérodiade. Vision fugitive -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Kathleen -- Old man river
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CFeb.2, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    Cap'n Stratton's Fancy -- Old man river
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CFeb.9, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    I cannot sing the old song -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Selections
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CFeb.9, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Sleigh -- Life begins with love
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CFeb.16, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Selections -- Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Hamlet. O vin, dissipe la tristesse
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CFeb.16, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Invictus -- Brown October ale
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CFeb.23, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Three for Jack -- Night and day
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.2, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 19)
    Moonlight Madonna -- Road to Mandalay
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.2, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 20)